<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Algorave on Maria Witek, DPhil</title>
    <link>/tags/algorave/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Algorave on Maria Witek, DPhil</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/algorave/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New SoundCloud</title>
      <link>/livecoding/soundcloud_2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/livecoding/soundcloud_2020/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VR Algorave at Network Music Festival</title>
      <link>/livecoding/c_nmf_2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/livecoding/c_nmf_2020/</guid>
      <description>Since the global lockdown due to the coronavirus pandemic, many music events have had to move their performances online. The Network Music Festival is an event that has been organinsing online music events for years! It was a real treat to play at their VR algorave, hosted in a cyber wearhouse and co-organised by Toplap Berlin. Antonio (hellocatfood) and I (mxwx) played some brand new stuff using TidalCycles, accompanied by some glithy furry visuals made in Pure Data and Gem by Patrick Valiquet (The Animalizer).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eulerroom Equinox Live Stream</title>
      <link>/livecoding/d_eul_2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/livecoding/d_eul_2020/</guid>
      <description>March 2020 was the month that many people around the world went into lockdown due to the global COVID-19 pandemic. It was a stressfull time, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t know when I&amp;rsquo;d get to see my friends and family again. Just by coincidence, the live-coding community were hosting an online event; The Eulerroom Equinox Live Stream. Social distancing felt a little less depressing when I could watch my friends and colleagues make incredible music and visuals on the stream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coventry Algorave</title>
      <link>/livecoding/b_coventry_2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/livecoding/b_coventry_2019/</guid>
      <description>At Coventry&amp;rsquo;s first ever Algorave, on July 16th 2019 at the Herbert Art Gallery and Museum, Antonio Roberts (hellocatfood) and I (mxwx) live coded music collaboratively using Troop and TidalCycles, with Carol Breen (imagemover) on visuals. This was my first ever public live coding/algorave performance. We performed among other excellent live coders, Lucy Cheesman (Heavy Lifting) and Innocent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ICLC Algorave Limerick</title>
      <link>/livecoding/a_limerick_2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/livecoding/a_limerick_2020/</guid>
      <description>Another great experience live coding as mxwx collaboratively with Antonio Roberts (hellocatfood), using Troop and TidalCycles. The Algorave was on the last evening of the International Conference for Live Coding (ICLC) in Limerick, Ireland, February 7th 2020. So many excellent performances that night! You can catch the archived live stream of the event here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>